AITA for telling my best friend I’m not comfortable being
her unpaid therapist? My best friend, 26F, has been going
through a tough time with her job and relationship. I’ve
tried to be there for her, listening patiently, offering advice,
and even checking in daily. But lately, it’s starting to
feel like every interaction is a dumping ground for her
problems. I’d gently suggested that she might benefit from talking
to a professional or joining a support group. As I’m
feeling emotionally drained, she got upset, saying I’m
supposed to be her support system and that I’m abandoning
her in her time of need. I care about her
deeply, but I’m also have my own mental health to
consider. Is it wrong to set boundaries and encourage her
to seek help from someone trained to handle this stuff,
or am I being a bad friend by not continually
providing emotional labor for free? AITA?